{
  "abhi": [
    {
      "question": "Who are your primary influencers?",
      "answer": "I know this is a pretty stock answer, but my primary influencers must be
      my parents. Their life journeys have taken them from small-town India to
      the U.S., where they’ve really epitomized the American Dream. I never
      really gave them credit for the courage and persistence they embodied as
      they embarked on their adventure, raised a family, and became successful
      doctors. I've been fortunate to witness their growth as individuals, and
      I'm incredibly proud of them."
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you balance growing and strengthening your current business while
      looking for opportunities to innovate?",
      "answer": "I couldn’t agree more with that sentiment, but it’s so incredibly
      hard to find that balance. In my opinion, a lot of business leaders take their
      eyes off the ball and are always constantly chasing the latest and greatest
      new shiny object without really focusing enough on cultivating the business
      they have. I’ve seen far more businesses fail by stretching themselves too
      thin and trying to grow bigger and better in a hurry than I have businesses
      who fail because they focused too much on their current business.
      <br /><br />
      I find that those businesses who are disciplined and have incredible focus
      are ultimately those that “win”, so I would lean towards really ensuring that
      you’ve cultivated your current business to it’s greatest extent before moving
      on to the next big innovation. "
    },
    {
      "question": "What would you say has been the defining moment for you as a
      business leader to this point in your career?",
      "answer": "I don’t know if I have a singular defining moment. I believe that
       the notion of there being a singular “aha moment” or something similar is a
       false one. One of the moments that I am most proud of was when we became
       profitable. It had been a long, winding, harrowing road to get there -
       and it’s not something a lot of startups ever accomplish. It certainly
       wasn’t the end of the road, but it validated our business model."
    },
    {
      "question": "What drives you to take on the challenges of running a business?",
      "answer": "The biggest thing that drives me to take on the challenge of
      running the business is the sheer amount of experience and knowledge I gain
      from this process. I don’t know if I’ll ever learn as much as I have been
      able to running my own business. It’s like a PhD, an MBA,  and a bunch of
      other degrees all rolled up into one incredible experience. "
    },
    {
      "question": "What book is on your kindle or playing on audible right now?",
      "answer": "I’m listening to “American Gods” by Neil Gaiman. I’ve always been
      fascinated by ancient cultures, their belief systems, and specifically their
      mythologies. American Gods is a really innovative take on the clash between
      traditional beliefs and religion vs. modern society and culture. "
    }
  ],
  "collin": [
    {
      "question": "Who are your primary influencers?",
      "answer": "I have several. My family and my team are my immediate influencers, but in terms of who I admire the most in the ‘business' world: Gary Vaynerchuk. "
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you balance growing and strengthening your current business while
      looking for opportunities to innovate?",
      "answer": "I focus on building the best team I can.  If the team is always strong and bought into my vision, we will be able to face any adversity that may come our way.  The company is only as strong as the team and culture that is in place.  With the right people in place, because they are ‘running the show,’ I can focus my attention to new innovative revenue driving opportunities. "
    },
    {
      "question": "What would you say has been the defining moment for you as a
      business leader to this point in your career?",
      "answer": "When I split with my partner in January of 2006. The thoughts going through my head at the time —>  “Should I give myself a pat on the back and say ‘great effort’ and throw in the towel because this partnership failed?  Do I have what it takes to start all over and build this business up as the ‘only’ leader?  Are my friends and family going to look at me as a failure?” This was that defining moment for sure.  I started all over and have successfully built a team that has built one of the most influential scooter dealerships in the country. "
    },
    {
      "question": "What drives you to take on the challenges of running a business?",
      "answer": "The challenge itself drives me!  I actually feed off challenges.  I’m motivated by overcoming obstacles.  My entire entrepreneurial career has been challenged due to people telling me “You can’t” and “You won’t.”  I LOVE this and LOVE proving people wrong."
    },
    {
      "question": "What book is on your kindle or playing on audible right now?",
      "answer": "Entreleadership by Dave Ramsey"
    }
  ],
  "rick_carlson": [
    {
      "question": "Who are your primary influencers?",
      "answer": "Business - Steve Blank, Steve Jobs, Malcolm Gladwell<br />
      Personal - Sam Harris, Richard Dawkins, Steven Hawking"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you balance growing and strengthening your current business while
      looking for opportunities to innovate?",
      "answer": "Yes, always.  The process of building a business has as much to do with tearing down as it does building.  That means processes that worked today won’t necessarily work tomorrow, so they must be torn down and rebuilt to meet the current and future needs of the business.  The same is true of your product or service.  As a start-up you are obsessed with finding your initial “product/market fit.”  If you are both smart and lucky, you’ll find it.  Over time though, you come to the realization that you have to work to keep and/or improve that fit in order to stay competitive.  That comes in the form of innovation, and that means looking far enough into the future to react in time."
    },
    {
      "question": "What would you say has been the defining moment for you as a
      business leader to this point in your career?",
      "answer": "I cannot point to one defining moment.  My time as a leader has been filled with highs and lows, times when I felt like I did a great job, and times when I felt like I have failed.  It is a continual process of failing and succeeding, reflecting and leaning. Someday, I hope to be really, really good at it."
    },
    {
      "question": "What drives you to take on the challenges of running a business?",
      "answer": "I have a short attention span, and need to be challenged. I was honestly scared at the idea of doing the same thing for 40 years.  Despite the stress, the challenges of running a business have me looking forward to work every day."
    },
    {
      "question": "What book is on your kindle or playing on audible right now?",
      "answer": "The End of Faith by Sam Harris."
    }
  ],
  "chris_marhefka": [
    {
      "question": "Who are your primary influencers?",
      "answer": "I am a huge fan of the greats Jim Rohn, Zig Ziglar, Tony Robbins. I listen to their content and read their books on a regular basis. They are some of the biggest influencers in how I go about my business decisions and even day-to-day life."
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you balance growing and strengthening your current business while
      looking for opportunities to innovate?",
      "answer": "I think many times these are one in the same. You're constantly looking to grow your business and to do so you also must grow as an individual. This requires the foresight and knowledge of what is to come along with the discipline to get done today what needs to get done. All in all I think it's about balance. You can't spend so much time in the clouds dreaming of what could be that you forget what's in front of you, and you can't spend so much time on the day to day tasks you forget to plan ahead and dream for the future."
    },
    {
      "question": "What would you say has been the defining moment for you as a
      business leader to this point in your career?",
      "answer": "I feel that my success has been more a factor of small wins than a large breakthrough, but the largest impact came when I started turning to other people. The moment I shifted my mindset and started reading business books, hiring a business coach, joined a mastermind, and asked for help was when things really changed for me. Not only did my business increase in revenue, but I grew and became more productive and started working smarter. Learning from those around you, whether it be an Executive who makes millions a year or a worker at a local grocery store, doesn't mean you don't have what it takes it means your humble and realistic enough to know you don't know everything and everyone has something they can offer you."
    },
    {
      "question": "What drives you to take on the challenges of running a business?",
      "answer": "My wife once told me I have one setting, \"Go!\" I think she hit the nail on the head because honestly, I wouldn't have it any other way. I thrive in an environment where I'm under pressure and have to rise to the occasion. This makes running a business the perfect challenge for me."
    },
    {
      "question": "What book is on your kindle or playing on audible right now?",
      "answer": "I am definitely an Audible fan and listen to over 50 a year. Currently, I'm listening to \"Shoe Dog: A Memoir by the Creator of Nike\" By Phil Knight and \"Letters from a Self-Made Merchant to his Son\" By George Horace Lorimer"
    }
  ],
  "geoff_wilson": [
    {
      "question": "Who are your primary influencers?",
      "answer": "My dad and some business leaders in Gainesville who I learned from (Joe Cirulli, Rich Blaser, Tim Broom, Nelson Logan, etc.) while part of the Vistage Group in Gainesville. I have also been influenced by certain authors with great business and startup advice -- in particular, Seth Godin, Patrick Lencioni, Eric Reis and Simon Sinek. And I love the story of Ben & Jerry's."
    },
    {
      "question": "It has been said that you need to cultivate both the business you have and the business you will have or risk being out of business. How do you balance growing and strengthening your current business while looking for opportunities to innovate?",
      "answer": "This is true. Your company has to have a mindset of growth and agility. I tell my team that we are a 20-year-old startup. That's the mentality we need to maintain. Working in teams helps, and having a flat org chart helps. You have to really empower your teams to take ownership, make decisions and be self-sufficient. The more layers of management and bureaucracy you have, the further away you will get from this."
    },
    {
      "question": "What would you say has been the defining moment for you as a business leader to this point in your career?",
      "answer": "I don't think there is ever one defining moment because growing a business is a journey. There is no end destination or single moment that will make or break you. To be successful, you need a lot of small steps forward that will add up to chart a successful path. You will always have steps backwards too, but if you have enough small steps forward you'll overcome the setbacks."
    },
    {
      "question": "What drives you to take on the challenges of running a business?",
      "answer": "The ability to create my own future and to create opportunities for others. Running a business is hard; you need to have an inner calling to achieve something great to overcome the setbacks."
    },
    {
      "question": "What book is on your kindle or playing on audible right now?",
      "answer": "I listen to podcasts more than I read books. I am really enjoying Malcolm Gladwell's Revisionist History right now. I also recommend Seth Godin's startup school, some of Tim Ferris' interviews, How I Built This, and the Y Combinator podcasts."
    }
  ]
}
